Guide to the Administrative Papers of the President George Bugliarello RG.006
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series III: Polytechnic
  - Subseries G: Board Members, 1968-1990
    - Adler, Benjamin (Emeritus), 1975 June-1990 July (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Albert, Sidney G., 1985 June-1989 March (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Angermueller, Hans H., 1985 September-1988 December (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Baclini, David, 1979 September-1986 April (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Bloom, Jeremiah B., 1980 January-1983 October (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Brown, Joseph D., 1975 June, 1980 June (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Bruynes, Cees, 1983 July-1989 May (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Buchanan, Harry W., 1979 June-1987 August (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Catacosinos, William, 1980 October-1984 October (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Conigliaro, Salvatore A., Undated (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Dalton, Philip B., 1979 July-December (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Dibner, Bern, Honorary Trustee, 1979 November-1988 August (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Fromm, Dr. Winfield E., 1978 August-1983 July (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Gavin, Joseph G., 1976 January-1983 November (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Habach, George F., Emeritus Trustee, 1973 September-1989 May (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Hickey, Frank, 1980 May-1981 March (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Hoffman, Harmon F., 1979 September–1987 August (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Laubach, Gerald D., 1980 October–1987 May (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Leistner, William E., 1968 May-1990 March (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Lewis, Dr. Robert E. (Emeritus), 1975 June-1983 July (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Llewelyn-Davies, Richard, 1978 June-1981 June (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Mark, Herman F., 1975 June-1989 May (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Mitchel, David C., 1975 June, 1984 July (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Newman, Joseph, 1985 June-1988 July (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Nisenson, Stanley M., 1983 August-1987 September (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Pascal, Donald D., 1975 June-1988 June (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Pighi, Louis H., 1983 July-1990 January (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Rogee, Dr. Herbert H., 1975 June-1977 September (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Simmonds, Geoffrey R., 1985 September-1986 December (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Smith, Harrison V., 1980 February-1988 July (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Westerman, David, 1980 March-1989 May (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Subseries H: Miscellaneous
    - Administrative Officer's Directory, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Agendas, 1993 June-August, 1994 January (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - Agendas, 1993 December (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Alumni Development & Fundraising, 1991-1993 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Annual Meeting of the Corporation, 1993 May 26 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Appointment Book, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - ASME Region II, Graduate Student Technical Conference, 1993 April 16 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - Board of Overseers – Peer Comparison, University of Pennsylvania, 1981 January-March (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - Board of Trustees Recruitment, 1990 December (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - Budget, 1991 March-1992 September (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - Budget, 1980-1983 (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - Car Phone, NYNEX, 1991 March (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - Center for Technology and Financial Services, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 52)
    - C.T.F. – Contacts, Undated (Box 30, Folder 53)
    - C.T.F. - Proposal, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 54)
    - C.T.F. – St. Johns, 1993 March-December, Undated (Box 30, Folder 55)
    - Center for Telecommunications Technology, Draft, Undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Chemistry Department, 1968 May-1975 March (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1975 November, 1979 April (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Clippings - Hi-Tech Universities, 1982 April-1983 April (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Clippings – Hi-Tech Universities, 1984 February-1985 June (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Clipping Book, 1980-1987 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Complaint - RESTRICT, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Contacts, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Corporation, 1993 March-December (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Corporation, 1994 January, March (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Corporation – Budget Reports, 1987 October-1992 October (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Corporation – Fiscal Year 1994 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Corporation – Miscellaneous, 1987 June-1992 March (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Corporation Annual Meeting Minutes, 1993 July 26 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Corporation Meeting, 1993 January 21 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Corporation Meetings, 1993 March-May (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Corporation Meetings, 1993 March-1994 April (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1976 December–1977 May (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1977 March-December (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1978 February-September (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1978 September (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1992 May-October (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1990 February-1993 June (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1991 June-1993 December (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1992 February–1993 December (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1992 December-1993 July (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1992 May-1993 June (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1993 May-September (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1993 December-1994 April (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1993 January-1994 March (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1993 October-1994 March (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, Undated (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence - Regis University, 1993 November 12 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Course Development – Engineering, 1992 November (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - C.W. Hoover, 1992 November (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Department of Civil Engineering Corporation Visiting Committee, 1989 May-1992 November (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Departmental Reports, 1987 December-1990 August (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Development - Jeffrey Stewart Visit, 1993 March (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Development – Memorandum, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Development - Paul Steck Visit, 1993 February-March (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Development Committee, 1992 September-1994 January (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Directions To/From Campus, Undated (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Donations, 1990 December (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Eli Pearce - N.Y. Institute of Chemists Awards, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Engineering Colleges, Legislatures and Community, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - Engineering Department 5-year Plan, 1981-1986 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Engineering, Science & Management Education, 1986 April (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Enrollment Memo, 1994 February (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1992 November 24 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Expenses, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Faculty, 1989 September-1992 November (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Financial Services Technology Consortium (FINTECH), 1993 June (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Fiscal Year Budgets, 1991-1994 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Fundraising, 1984-1989 April (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Fundraising, 1987 December-1988 November, Undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Fundraising - Poly 100 Newsletter, 1994 Winter (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Grant Proposals – National Science Foundation, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Holiday Cards, 1992, Undated (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Holiday Gift from the Bugliarellos, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Honorary Degree Recipients, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Inaugural Address – Technology, the University and the Community, 1975 March 13 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - The Intelligent Layman's Guide to Technology, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - International Student Orientation, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Invoices, 1992 April-October (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Kyoto University – Poly Academic Exchange, 1990 April-1992 June (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Leadership Candidates, 1988 August (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Letter to the Faculty, Drafts, 1989 July-August (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - L.I.C. Farmingdale, 1993 May 13 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - L.I.C. Westinghouse Site Acquisition, 1993 January (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Marconi International Fellowship, 1992 October (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Meeting, 1992 November 16 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Meeting of the Corporation, 1993 January 21 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Members of the Corporation, Lists, 1977-1986 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Memo to the Corporation, Draft, 1990 March (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Memos – Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Microwave Research Institute, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Middle States Association – Accreditation Visit Spring 1992 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Middle States Association, 1982 June, 1987 June (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Middle States Association, 1990 April-November (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous, 1985; 1989 July-1992 October (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992 June, 1993 September (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993 January-May (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - New Initiatives Meeting, 1994 November (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - New Poly Curriculum – George Bugliarello Notes & Research, 1980 May-1985 January (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - New Poly Curriculum – George Bugliarello Notes & Research, 1985 February-May, Undated (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Office of the President – Purchasing, 1992 August-December (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Office of University Development – Correspondence, 1958 February-1975 December (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Office of the University Relations – Strategic Plan, 1992 April 27 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Overheads for Alumni Association Annual Meeting, 1990 June 11 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1977 March (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Phone Directories – Trustees & All University, 1988-1992 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - President's Associates List, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - President's Financial Statements, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - President's Report to the Corporation, 1975-1988, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Presidential Search, 1991 March-December (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Professional Appointment Book, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Professional Appointment Book, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Professional Appointment Book, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Professional Appointment Book, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Professional Appointment Calendar (Weekly), 1990 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Promise Fund / Poly 100, 1993 March-May (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Promise Fund Distinguished Service Award, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Promotional Material, 1978, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Promotional Material, 1988, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Promotional Material, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Promotional Material, 1993-1994 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Proposal to Teagle Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Publication – Invention and Education, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Report to Trustees, Drafts, 1988 May-1989 December (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Research at Poly, an Overview, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Robert Meyers, Trustee – Correspondence, 1993 March (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Rudolph Marcus Nobel Prize, 1992 October (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - School of Engineering & Applied Sciences (SEAS) – Duke University model, 1980-1981 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Search Committee, Faculty Head, Computer Science, 1985 October (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Search Committee, Faculty Head, Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering, 1985 January-1986 March (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Search Committee, Physics Head, 1985 August (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Self Study, 1992 October-1993 March (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Space Electronics Institute, 1986 April (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Staff Bios - RESTRICT, Undated (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Stanley Prill – Dinner, 1993 July (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - State Education Department – Correspondence, 1993 September (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Strategic Assessment Proposal, KPMG, 1992 August (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Strategic Plan, 1992 October 1 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Strategic Planning Meeting, 1993 November (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Student Complaint - RESTRICT, 1993 January-February (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Student Contact Information - RESTRICT, 1991, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Student Council Meeting, 1989 July 12 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Student Handbook, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Suggestion Box, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Dr. Sun Honorary Degree, 1993 February-March (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Symposium – Polymer Science in the Next Decade, 1985 May (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Symposium Programs – Electrical Engineering & Computer Science, 1985 September (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Visiting Committee of the School of Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, 1993 November (Box 33, Folder 44)
- Series IV: Organizations
  This series is arranged topically into 8 subseries.
  This series contains correspondence, memoranda, clippings, articles, meeting minutes and miscellaneous documents documenting George Bugliarello's role as member, trustee and elected official of a wide array educational, scientific, governmental and social organizations and associations.
  - Subseries A: Analytic Services (ANSER), 1987-1993
    - ANSER - Correspondence, Memoranda, 1987 November-1989 January (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - ANSER - Correspondence, Memoranda, 1990 March-1991 September (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - ANSER - Correspondence, Memoranda, 1991 October-1992 April (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - ANSER - Correspondence, Memoranda, 1992 April-1993 February, Undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Subseries B: Board on Science & Technology for International Development (BOSTID)
    - BOSTID - Miscellaneous, 1975-1980 August (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - BOSTID - Miscellaneous, 1980 September-1981 May (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - BOSTID - Miscellaneous, 1981 September-December (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - BOSTID - Miscellaneous, 1982 January-April (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - BOSTID - Miscellaneous, 1982 May-November (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - BOSTID - Miscellaneous, 1982 December (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - BOSTID - Miscellaneous, 1983 January-November (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - BOSTID - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - BOSTID – Annual Program Plan, 1981 July 1-1982 June 30 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - BOSTID - Governing Board, 1980 October (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - BOSTID - Innovation Program, 1993 June (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - BOSTID - Meeting, 1982 Aril 23 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - BOSTID - Membership, 1980-1983 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - BOSTID - Retreat, 1983 June 24-26 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Subseries C: National Academy of Engineering (NAE)
    - National Academy of Engineering - Miscellaneous, 1989 December-1993 December (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - National Academy of Engineering - Miscellaneous, 1994 January-March (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - National Academy of Engineering - Correspondence, 1992 July (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - National Academy of Engineering – Infrastructure, 1989 May-1991 June, Undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - National Academy of Engineering - Nominations, 1975 March-1978, 1988; Undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - National Academy of Engineering - Steering Committee, 1978 November (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Subseries D: New York City Partnership, 1979-1995
    - NYC Partnership - Miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - NYC Partnership – Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - NYC Partnership – Miscellaneous, 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - NYC Partnership – Miscellaneous, 1984-1987 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - NYC Partnership – Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - NYC Partnership – Miscellaneous, 1989 May-June 14 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - NYC Partnership – Miscellaneous, 1989 June 19-December (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - NYC Partnership – Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - NYC Partnership – Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - NYC Partnership – Miscellaneous, 1992-1995 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - NYC Partnership – Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - NYC Partnership - Hi-Tech Committee, 1988-1990; Undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - NYC Partnership - BMD Trade Mission - Photographs, 1982 June (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - NYC Partnership – Technology Executive Council, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Subseries E: North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO)
    - Ankara, 1994 June (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Ankara Program, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Ankara, Turkey - Bios, 1993 December-1994 October (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Aytmatov, Dr. Ilgiz, 1994 March (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Belarus, 1994 April (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Brill, Yvonne C., 1994 March-June (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Budget, 1993 December-1996 February (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Bugliarello, Virginia, 1994 June (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Cadiou, Dr. Jean, 1993 September-1994 June (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Carroll, William, 1994 January-June (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Circular, 1994 June-July (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence - Follow-ups, 1994 February (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - David, Dr. Ed, 1993 September-1994 April (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - DiCataldo, Vincenzo, 1994 April (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Dineen, Dr. Gerald P., 1993 September-1994 March (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Erhan, Dr. Sevim, 1994 April (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Fabian, John M., 1993 July-1994 February (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Forsen, Dr. Harold K., 1994 January-February (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Gage, Carl, 1994 March-April (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Gordos, Dr. Geza, 1993 October -1994 June (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Greece, 1986 July -1990 September (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Greece, 1990 February-April (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Greece, 1992 July (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Greece, 1995 July-August (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Greek Polyblend, 1995 October, 1996 March (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Hemily, Philip W., 1993 October-1994 April (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Hertlein, Dr. H.P., 1994 June (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Jubier, Alain H., 1993 September-1994 June (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Kabanov, Victor A., 1993 June-1994 February (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Kazakhstan, 1993 September-1994 February (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Kazakhstan Course, 1995 February (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Kluwer Academic Publishers, 1994 January-1996 August (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Master, 1993 April-December; ` (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Master, 1993 March-1994 July (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989 May-December (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990 February-November (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990 December (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, 1991 March-April (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992 February-June (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993 January-November (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 January-June (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 July (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 August-November (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 December (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995 January-December (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996 April-1997 April (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Murino, Teresa, 1994 May-July (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Nalecz, Dr. Maciej, 1993 September-1994 March (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Nesvetailov, Dr. Gennady, 1994 April (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1985 February, 1993 January-November (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Ney, Andrew L. Esq., 1993 November (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - NSF, 1993 January-1994 July (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Poholkov, Yuri Petrovich, 1993 September-1994 May (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Rabkin, Professor Yakov M., 1993 November-1994 June (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Radosevic, Dr. Slavo, 1994 March-September (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Rambaut, Dr. Paul, 1994 June (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Russia, 1993 September-October (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Russian Space Agency, 1994 February-June (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Sahin, Dr. Faith, 1994 April (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Salakhitdinov, Professor M.S., 1994 January-April (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Salmon, William C., 1994 April-June (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Schillinger, Dr. George, 1994 May (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Schweitzer, Glenn, 1994 January-April (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Science for Stability Program, 1993 April-December (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Science for Stability Program, 1994 January-December (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Science for Stability Program - Program proposals, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Science for Stability Program – Program proposals, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Sherwood, Robert M., 1994 July (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Spiro, Jody, 1994 March-May (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Sultangazin, Dr. Omirzak Makhmutovich, 1994 March-June (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Syrbe, Dr. M., 1993 September (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Tishkov, Dr. K., 1994 April (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - TU-Black Sea, 1993 May (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - TU-Language Program, 1995 April-May (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Turkey, 1993 September-August (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Turkey, 1993 September-August (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Ukraine, 1993 October-1994 May (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - U.S. Embassies / Former USSR, 1994 May-June (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Vance, Elsie, 1994 March-April (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Warnecke, Dr. Ing. Hans Jurgen, 1994 March-July (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Zinberg, Dr. Dorothy, 1994 March-June (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Suberies F: Sigma Xi: The Scientific Research Society
    - Sigma Xi - Miscellaneous, 1991 April-November (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Sigma Xi - Miscellaneous, 1992 January-June (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Sigma Xi - Miscellaneous, 1992 July-September (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Sigma Xi - Miscellaneous, 1992 October-December (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Sigma Xi - Miscellaneous, 1993 January-December (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Sigma Xi - Miscellaneous, 1994 January-April (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Sigma Xi - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Sigma Xi - Ad Hoc Committee, 1992 August, 1993 January (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Sigma Xi - Capital Campaign, 1992 May-August (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Sigma Xi - Conference, 1991 November-1992 March (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Sigma Xi - Correspondence, 1992 June-September (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Sigma Xi - Correspondence, 1992 October (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Sigma Xi - Executive Committee, 1992 February 24 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Sigma Xi - Thomas F. Malone, 1992 October-December (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Subseries G: Teagle Foundation, 1986-1993
    - Teagle Foundation – Board Meetings, 1986 February-May, 1993 February (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Teagle Foundation – Miscellaneous, 1983 October-1987 December (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Teagle Foundation – Miscellaneous, 1988 February-September (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - Teagle Foundation – Miscellaneous, 1988 October-December (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Teagle Foundation – Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Teagle Foundation – Miscellaneous, 1990 January-April (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Teagle Foundation – Miscellaneous, 1990 May-December (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Teagle Foundation – Miscellaneous, 1991 January-February (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Teagle Foundation – Miscellaneous, 1991 April-December (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Teagle Foundation – Miscellaneous, 1992; Undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Subseries H: Miscellaneous, 1978-1995
    - American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics (AIAA) – Annual Meeting Panel, 1987 February-April (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Association of Independent Technological University (AITU), 1992-1993 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Board of Visitors – Duke University, 1992-1994 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Board of Overseers – School of Engineering and Applied Sciences - University of Pennsylvania, 1992 July -1994 March (Box 38, Folder 11)